Guide to the Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinsky and Lieberman Legal Files TAM.287
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Case Files, 1922-1988
  - Robeson, Paul, In the Matter of Passport Application: Complaint, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Robeson, Paul, In the Matter of Passport Application: Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Robeson, Paul, In the Matter of Passport Application: Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Robeson, Paul, In the Matter of Passport Application: Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Robeson, Paul, In the Matter of Passport Application: Transcript and Exhibits, 1956-1958 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Robeson, Paul v. Dulles, John Foster: Briefs, 1954-1956 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Robeson v. Dulles: Correspondence, 1950-1956 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Robeson v. Dulles: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Robeson v. Dulles: Exhibits, 1949-1957 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Robeson v. Dulles: Foreign Correspondence (Protests), 1953-1954 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Robeson v. Dulles: Formal File, 1952-1956 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Robeson v. Dulles: Passport Application, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Robeson v. Dulles: Pleadings, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Robeson v. Dulles: Record, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - In Re Rosenberg, Michael and Robert, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - In Re Sacher, Harold and Isserman, Maurice, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Samuels, George v. Mackel, Thomas(District Attorney of Queens County): Briefs, 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Samuels v. Mackell: Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Samuels v. Mackell: Fernandez v. Mackell, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Samuels v. Mackell: Formal (I), 1969-1974 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Samuels v. Mackell: Formal (II), 1967-1969 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Samuels v. Mackell: Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Schneider, Angelika v. Herter, Christian(U.S. Secretary of State), 1960 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Segall, John v. Jacobson, Nathan(Board of Education, City of New York): Briefs, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Sell, Evelyn, v. Austin Independent School District, et al., 1976-1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Selzer, Michael v. Berkowitz, Morton and Board of Higher Education of New York City, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Selzer v. Berkowitz, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Selzer v. Berkowitz, 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Selzer v. Berkowitz, 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Shachtman, Max v. Dulles, John Foster: Passport, Undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Shepherd, George, W. v. Dulles, John Foster: Passport, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Sierra Club, Southwest Research and Information Center, et al. v. New Mexico State Police, et al., 1982 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Silkwood, Karen v. Kerr-McGee Corporation(I), 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Silkwood v. Kerr-McGee(II), 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Silkwood v. Kerr-McGee(III), 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Silkwood v. Kerr-McGee(IV), 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Richard E. v. Denny, Charles F.(Enterprise High School), 1968 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Socialist Workers Party v. Brown, Edmund G.(I), 1974 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Socialist Workers Party v. Brown(II), 1974 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Socialist Workers Party v. Chicago Police, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Socialist Workers Party v. Rochford, James, et al., 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al., 1973 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al.(I), 1974 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al.(II), 1974 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al., 1974-1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al., 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al., 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al.(I), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al.(II), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al.(III), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al.- Excerpts Pre-1960 Surveillance, 1976-1980 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al.- Kelley, Clarence Deposition, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Socialist Workers Party, et al. v. Attorney General, et al.- Original Exhibits (Political Candidates List), 1948-1980 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Spock, Benjamin v. USA: Briefs, 1970s-1980s (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Spock v. USA: Correspondence, 1975-1990 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Spock v. USA: Court Documents, ca.1976-1980 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Spock v. USA: Court Documents, ca.1976-1981 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Spock v. USA: Court Documents (I), 1976-1980 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Spock v. USA: Court Documents (II), 1976-1980 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Spock v. USA: Court Documents, ca.1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Spock v. USA: Court Documents (I), 1970s-1980s (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Spock v. USA: Court Documents (II), 1970s-1980s (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Spock v. USA: Court Documents (III), 1970s-1980s (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Spock v. USA: Memos, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Spock v. USA: Press, 1979-1982 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Stapp, Andrew D., U.S. Army Proceedings of a Board of Inquiry: Fort Sill, Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Starsky, Morris, v. Williams, Jack, et al.(I), 1976 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Starsky v. Williams, et al.(II), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Starsky v. Williams, et al.(III), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Steiger, Andrew J.: Passport Appeal, 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Steinmatz, Harry C. v. California State Board of Education, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 3a)
  - Stewart, Donald Ogden v. Dulles, John Foster: Correspondence (I), 1956-1958 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Stewart v. Dulles: Correspondence (II), 1956-1958 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Stewart v. Dulles: Correspondence (Ella), 1952-1956 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Stewart v. Dulles: Donald Ogden Steward Jr., 1956 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Stewart v. Dulles: Formal, 1956-1958 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Stewart v. Dulles: Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Stewart v. Dulles: Miscellaneous News Coverage, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Straus, Dudley David v. New York City Board of Education: Briefs, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Straus v. NYC Board of Education: Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Straus v. NYC Board of Education: Exhibits and Report, 1953-1955 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Straus v. NYC Board of Education: Legal File, 1955-1956 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Straus v. NYC Board of Education: Related Case, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Tobias, Harris v. Laird, Melvin(I), 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Tobias v. Laird(II), 1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Turner, William v. International Association of Machinists(IAM): Briefs and Filings, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Turner v. IAM: IAM v. Turner Expulsion Documents, 1975-1977 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Turner v. IAM: Research, Notes, Correspondence, and Drafts, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Ullman, William Ludwig v. United States of America: Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Ullman v. USA: Formal File: Supreme Court, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Ullman v. USA: Supreme Court Correspondence, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Ungar, Sidney(Attorney Disciplinary Proceedings), 1964 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - United States of America v. Achtenberg, Joel: Formal, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Achtenberg: Legal Research, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - United States of America v. Ahmad, Eqbal, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Ahmad, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Feb 1971-Apr 1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Apr 1971-May 1971 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Ahmad, May 1971 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Apr 1971-May 1971 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Jun 1971 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Jun 1971-Aug 1971 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Aug 1971 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Sep 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Jan 1972 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Jan 1972-Feb 1972 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Ahmad, Mar 1972 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Argument, May 1905 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Correspondence, May 1905-1974 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents (I), 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents (II), 1972 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents (III), 1970-1972 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents (IV), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents (V), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Docket Sheets, 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Handwriting Examples, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Motions for Disclosure of Electronic Surveillance, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Motion to Dismiss, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Motions re: Effective Consultations, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Motions re Grand Jury, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Order to Show Cause, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Subpoenas, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Court Documents - Financial, 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Harrisburg Defense Committee, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Hearing Transcript, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Jury Selection, 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Letters, ca.1970 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Letters/Phone Records, 1970-1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Post Trial Court File, 1971-1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Post Trial Court File, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Post Trial Telephone Calls, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Post Trial Transcript, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Voice Identification, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Research (I), 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Research (II), 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Telephone Records, 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript - Partial, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 1, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 2, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 3, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 4, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 5, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 6, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 9, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 10, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 11, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 12, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 13, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 14, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 15, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 16, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 17, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 18, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 21, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Transcript Vol. 29, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Ahmad: Voir Dire, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - USA v. American Telephone and Telegraph Company, et al., 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Antonelli, Dominic and Joseph Yeldell, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Avakian, Robert B.(Mao Tse-tung Defendants): Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Avakian: Formal (I), 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Avakian: Formal (II), 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Avakian: Press, 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Alvelo, Sixto, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Ayers, William et al.(I), 1973 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Ayers(II), 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Ayers(III), 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Bissinger, Karl, et al.: Briefs, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Bissinger: Miscellaneous (War Resisters League; Washington Eleven), 1979 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Buckalew, Terry E., et al., 1973 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - USA v. City of Philadelphia, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Coffin, William Sloan, Jr.; USA v. Spock, Benjamin: Analysis of Record, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Bills, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Correspondence (I), 1968 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Correspondence (II), 1968 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Court Documents (I), 1968 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Court Documents (II), 1968 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Court Documents, 1960s (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Court Documents, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Defendants Exhibits (Pre-Trial and Trial), 1960s (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Document List, Undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Exhibits, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Government Exhibits, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Government Exhibits, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Government's Pre-Trial Exhibits, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Jury Materials, 1960s (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Memos, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Notes, ca.1968 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Personal - David McReynolds, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Personal - Benjamin Spock, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Research, 1967-1971 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Research, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Research, ca.1968 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Statements of Arrested Protestors, 1960s (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Testimony of Spock, 1964-1968 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript - Appendix, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. 1), 1968 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. II), 1968 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. IV), 1968 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. V), 1968 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. VI), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. VII), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. VIII), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. IX), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. X), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. XI), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. XII), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. XIII), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. XIV), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. XV), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. XVI), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. XVIII), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript of Trial (Vol. XX), 1968 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Transcript Summary, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Witness, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Coffin; USA v. Spock: Witness, 1960s (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Coffin &….Spock: Appeal, 1968-1969 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Colson, Charles(USA v. Russo, Nixon), 1974 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Connally, John B., 1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Felt, Mark and Edward Miller(I), 1980 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Felt(II), 1980 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Felt(III), 1980 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Felt(IV), 1980 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Felt(V), 1980 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Field, Frederick V.: Court Documents, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Field: Senate Hearings, 1951-1952 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Field: State Banking Department, 1951-1957 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Foster, William Z.(Communist Party), 1948-1949 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - USA v. Gibson, Berman; USA v. Hensley, Bige: Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Gibson; USA v. Hensley: Formal File: District Court, 1963-1967 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Gibson; USA v. Hensley: Formal File: Court of Appeals, 1964-1967 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Gibson; USA v. Hensley: Formal File: Supreme Court Petition for Rehearing, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Gibson; USA v. Hensley: Research, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Giese, Frank Stearns(I), 1971-1976 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Giese(I), 1974-1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Giese(II), 1974-1979 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Giese, 1976-1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Giese, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Giese, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Grafals, Edwin Feliciano(I), 1967-1970 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Grafals(II), 1967-1970 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Grafals(III), 1967-1970 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - USA v. Grafals, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - USA v. Grafals, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - USA v. Hillard, David, 1969-1971 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Hoff, Charles, et al.: Briefs (I), 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Hoff: Briefs (II), 1969-1975 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Hoff: Briefs (III), 1969-1975 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Hoff: Conspiracy, Undated, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Hoff: Drafts, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Hoff: Extra Formal Papers, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Hoff: General, 1969-1974 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Hoff: Glasser Testimony, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Hoff: Grand Jury Motion, 1971-1974 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Hoff: Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Hoff: Tax Evasion Count, 1961-1974 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Argument, Stofsky-direct), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Closing Statements), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Glasser cross and re-direct examination), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Glass Direct), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Grossman, Siegel), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Hoff, Hecht, Katcher), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Levy, Gold, Thylan, Hoff - direct), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (robing room conference, Glasser, Ginsberg, Reiss, Anolik, Stiel), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Silberweig, Grossman, Poulos, Cammer, Jaffee, Passaretti), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Hoff: Trial Transcripts (Stofsky, Hecht, Lageoles), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Hoff: Voluntary Commitment, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Kauffman, Joseph: Appellate Exhibits, Undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Kauffman: Brief, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Kauffman: Briefs (Kaufman v. Secretary of the Air Force), 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Kauffman: Formal File, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Kearney, John(I), 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Kearney(II), 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Kogan, Larry: Briefs, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Kogan: Briefs ( The Washington University Corporation v. Kerry Koch, et al.), 1970 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Kogan: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Kogan: Formal, 1970-1972 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Kogan: Instructions to the Jury, Undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Kogan: Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Kogan: Press Coverage, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - USA v. Laub, Lee Levi, et al.: Bail Enlargement Appeal, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - USA v. Laub Bail Enlargement Applications Formal, 1963-1966 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - USA v. Laub: Briefs (I), 1963 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - USA v. Laub: Briefs (II), 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Laub: Briefs (III), 1963 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Laub: Briefs, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Laub: Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Laub: Exhibits, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Laub: Formal, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Laub: Miscellaneous, 1961-1966 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Laub: Legal Research, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Laub, Lee Levi(Second Conspiracy Case): Correspondence, 1964-1865 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Laub(Second Conspiracy Case): Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Laub(Second Conspiracy Case): Formal, 1964-1967 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Laub(Second Conspiracy Case): Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Marshall, Charles Clark: Briefs and Bail papers, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - USA v. John Doe in the Matter of Idella Marx(Electronic Surveillance), 1971 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - USA v. Nuchow, William, et al: Appellant's Appendix, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Nuchow: Briefs, 1972-1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Nuchow: Formal (I), 1973 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Nuchow: Formal (II), 1973 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Nuchow: Mary Lampson, 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Paley, Grace(USA v. Bissinger): War Resisters League (Washington Eleven), 1980 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Pioggia, Joseph C., et al., 1984 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Powell, John: Briefs, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Powell: Correspondence, 1957-1980 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Powell: Press, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Progressive, The(I), 1979 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - USA v. Progressive, The(II), 1979 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz, Joni: Allen Decision, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Briefs, 1963-1966 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Correspondence, Aug 1963- Nov 1963 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Correspondence, Dec 1963-Aug 1964 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Correspondence, Sep 1964-1967 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Formal File, May 1905-May 1905 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Legal Research - General, May 1905-1966 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Legal Research - Jury Trial, Undated, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Legal Research - Jury Waiver, Undated, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Macon Indictments, 1954-1964 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - USA v. Rabinowitz: Macon Indictments, Undated, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 11)